{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. The price of a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ is the same as that of a creme brulee at Urban Plate. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. A creme brulee at Urban Plate and 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 22 dollars. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, pie at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ, 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ, a pie at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pies at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place. A burger at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A burger at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 49 dollars. 3 burgers at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 57 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 31 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, pie at Mike's Place, pie at Urban Plate are: 3 burgers at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 57 dollars, a pie at Mike's Place costs 31 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 3 pies at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and a pie at Mike's Place cost 17 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. 2 pies at Mike's Place and a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 30 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate, lasagna at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Mike's Place are: a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 30 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place, 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 75 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars less than a lasagna at Urban Plate. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 25 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, lasagna at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars less than a lasagna at Urban Plate, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate, 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars, 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 25 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 50 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 42 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Bistro Nice are: 2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine, a pie at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars, a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 13 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 22 dollars more than a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place are: 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 22 dollars more than a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 3 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 61 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost a dollar more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 61 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice, 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 28 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pies at Bistro Nice and a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 33 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 10 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Bistro Nice, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine, a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pies at Bistro Nice and a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars, 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 33 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 56 dollars. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars less than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 34 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ are: 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 56 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 28 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 33 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 7 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 7 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost 46 dollars. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice. 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost 46 dollars, 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 31 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. The price of a lasagna at Texas BBQ is the same as that of a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Mike's Place are: 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place, 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A pie at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 30 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice. A fruit tart at Mike's Place and a pie at Bistro Nice cost 25 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, pie at Bistro Nice are: 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 30 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place, a fruit tart at Mike's Place and a pie at Bistro Nice cost 25 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 50 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. A lasagna at Urban Plate and 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 23 dollars. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine, a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. A fruit tart at Mike's Place and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 45 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars, a fruit tart at Mike's Place and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. A pizza at Texas BBQ and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 19 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 19 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Mike's Place, pizza at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place are: a creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 19 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place, 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 19 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a creme brulee at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Mike's Place. 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 2 pies at Mike's Place. 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Mike's Place are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars, 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 2 pies at Mike's Place, a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 8 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 20 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 37 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 26 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 20 dollars, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 37 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ, 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 26 dollars, a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. A lasagna at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 46 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 22 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. A pizza at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Bistro Nice, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 22 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice, a pizza at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 46 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 46 dollars, 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 67 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 52 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars, 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 52 dollars, 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 67 dollars, 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Mike's Place and a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 19 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 31 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 50 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Mike's Place, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 burgers at Mike's Place and a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars, 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost a dollar more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars more than a burger at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, lasagna at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate are: 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. 2 burgers at Texas BBQ and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate are: 2 burgers at Texas BBQ and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars, 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars more than a burger at Bistro Nice. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 24 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 22 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, burger at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice are: 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars, a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 24 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 22 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars more than a burger at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 23 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 75 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 75 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate, 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ, a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 22 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Bistro Nice are: a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 22 dollars, 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 4 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 31 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 11 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars less than 3 pies at Urban Plate. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, pie at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Bistro Nice are: 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars less than 3 pies at Urban Plate, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 11 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate, a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 4 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice, a pie at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 31 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 11 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 52 dollars. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 57 dollars, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 11 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 52 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice, a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 23 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 28 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ. 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ, 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 23 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ, 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 81 dollars. A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. A pizza at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 32 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: a pizza at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate, a lasagna at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 81 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 49 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a burger at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars. The price of a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Urban Plate are: a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 49 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, the price of a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars, a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and a pie at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 46 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 pies at Urban Plate. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, pie at Urban Plate, pie at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Urban Plate are: 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars, 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate, 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and a pie at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars, 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 pies at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than 2 pies at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, lasagna at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, pie at Mike's Place are: 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ, 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than 2 pies at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost 36 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars. The price of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 51 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost 36 dollars, the price of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 51 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a burger at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 2 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 69 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place and 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Urban Plate, burger at Mike's Place, burger at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate are: 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a burger at Mike's Place, 2 burgers at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 69 dollars, 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate, 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. A burger at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and a burger at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. 3 pies at Urban Plate and a pizza at Bistro Nice cost 40 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and a burger at Bistro Nice cost 44 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, pie at Bistro Nice, burger at Bistro Nice, pizza at Urban Plate are: 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and a burger at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars, a burger at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and a burger at Bistro Nice cost 44 dollars, a pie at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ. 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a fruit tart at Mike's Place. A pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and a fruit tart at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Mike's Place, pie at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place are: 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and a fruit tart at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars, 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a fruit tart at Mike's Place, 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ, 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars less than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place are: a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 60 dollars, a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. The price of 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 34 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, pizza at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice and 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 34 dollars, 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A burger at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than a burger at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place. 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 29 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Mike's Place are: 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place, a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 29 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than a burger at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 45 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 17 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 23 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place are: a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 45 dollars, 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 17 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 55 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 38 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 38 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 55 dollars, a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars more than a Greek salad at Urban Plate. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice and a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost 30 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars. The price of a burger at Urban Plate is the same as that of a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars, 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, the price of a burger at Urban Plate is the same as that of a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars more than a Greek salad at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 4 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Texas BBQ are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 42 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 2 pies at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, burger at Taste Good Cuisine are: a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 2 pies at Urban Plate, 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate, 2 burgers at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars, 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost a dollar more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Urban Plate. A pizza at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, pizza at Texas BBQ, pizza at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ are: a pizza at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost a dollar more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, a pizza at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs a dollar less than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 39 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 50 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate are: 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate, a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs a dollar less than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 39 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars. A lasagna at Bistro Nice and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than 2 pies at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, pie at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place are: 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice, a lasagna at Bistro Nice and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars, a pie at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 29 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 46 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pizza at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, pizza at Texas BBQ are: 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice, a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 29 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice, 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 46 dollars, a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars more than a Greek salad at Mike's Place. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A burger at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Mike's Place are: 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars more than a Greek salad at Mike's Place, 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, a fruit tart at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost 25 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, a Greek salad at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost 25 dollars, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Bistro Nice. 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 36 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 49 dollars. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a fruit tart at Urban Plate. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 36 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars more than a Greek salad at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Bistro Nice, 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 36 dollars, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars more than a Greek salad at Bistro Nice, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 36 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 30 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 32 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 30 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place, 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place, a Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 32 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. The price of 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 34 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars. 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, pizza at Mike's Place are: 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars, the price of 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Mike's Place. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 21 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars. 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost a dollar more than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place. A pizza at Urban Plate costs a dollar less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. The price of a pizza at Urban Plate is the same as that of a pie at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, pie at Mike's Place are: 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost a dollar more than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars less than a pie at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 31 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 49 dollars. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars less than a burger at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 19 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Urban Plate, burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars less than a burger at Texas BBQ, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars, 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, 3 burgers at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 49 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost 46 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 40 dollars. 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 36 dollars. 3 pies at Texas BBQ and 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 pies at Texas BBQ and 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 36 dollars, 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 29 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 36 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 29 dollars, a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 36 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place, 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 27 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a lasagna at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Urban Plate, lasagna at Mike's Place, lasagna at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate, a Caesar salad at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 27 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place, a lasagna at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 51 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars more than a pie at Mike's Place. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars less than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place are: 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars less than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars more than a pie at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 51 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a pizza at Urban Plate. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 52 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a pizza at Urban Plate, 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars, 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 52 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars, a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 29 dollars less than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars more than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate. A pie at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a burger at Urban Plate. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Urban Plate, pie at Texas BBQ are: 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a burger at Urban Plate, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate, a pie at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Urban Plate and a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 8 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 13 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and a burger at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, lasagna at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and a burger at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 8 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Urban Plate and a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A burger at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars less than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 19 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: a Greek salad at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 19 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars, 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 55 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 58 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 35 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 55 dollars, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 35 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 78 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars less than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars less than a lasagna at Bistro Nice, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars, 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars, 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 78 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars less than a burger at Urban Plate. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A burger at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 34 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 25 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 35 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Urban Plate, burger at Mike's Place are: a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 34 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place, a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 25 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate, a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 35 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost a dollar less than 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 33 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 21 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than a pizza at Mike's Place. 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, pizza at Texas BBQ are: a Greek salad at Texas BBQ and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars, 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost a dollar less than 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place, a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 21 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars more than a pizza at Mike's Place. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 54 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars. 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 5 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 23 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 28 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, pie at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Texas BBQ are: 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars, a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 23 dollars, 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 28 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate. 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Urban Plate. 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine and a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 22 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A burger at Mike's Place costs 39 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. A pizza at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 50 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, pizza at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 22 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place, a pizza at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 50 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 43 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 5 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Urban Plate. 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars, a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine, a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 43 dollars, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Urban Plate and 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Urban Plate. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate and 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 26 dollars. The price of 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. The price of a burger at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a burger at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Bistro Nice are: a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Urban Plate, a Greek salad at Urban Plate and 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 26 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, a Cobb salad at Urban Plate and 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars, the price of 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 53 dollars. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Urban Plate, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Urban Plate are: a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 53 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a burger at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 31 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place are: 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars, 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place. 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place, 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars, 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place, 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 59 dollars. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a burger at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 72 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 30 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, burger at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Bistro Nice are: 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 59 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 72 dollars, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 30 dollars, a creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a burger at Urban Plate.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 50 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 17 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. A pizza at Texas BBQ and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs a dollar less than a pizza at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pizza at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, pizza at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 17 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 50 dollars, 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, a pizza at Texas BBQ and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars, a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs a dollar less than a pizza at Urban Plate.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 35 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A pie at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 35 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a pie at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 24 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars less than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pies at Texas BBQ and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 70 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 34 dollars less than 3 pies at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a pie at Taste Good Cuisine, a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 34 dollars less than 3 pies at Texas BBQ, 2 pies at Texas BBQ and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 70 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 24 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 40 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ. The price of 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars more than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, the price of 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate, a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pie at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than a fruit tart at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. The price of 3 pies at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 4 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate are: 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than a fruit tart at Urban Plate, 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, the price of 3 pies at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars less than a pizza at Mike's Place. 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. A pizza at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, pizza at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars less than a pizza at Mike's Place, a pizza at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and a fruit tart at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 28 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars more than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 26 dollars. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and a fruit tart at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars more than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost 28 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 52 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 49 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, lasagna at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice, 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate, a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 49 dollars, 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate are: a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 23 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 20 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Urban Plate are: 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate, 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate, a creme brulee at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars, a creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 23 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than a pie at Mike's Place. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 20 dollars less than 2 burgers at Bistro Nice. A pie at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars. 3 pies at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, pie at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Mike's Place, pie at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place are: a pie at Bistro Nice costs a dollar more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, 3 pies at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than a pie at Mike's Place, a pie at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a pizza at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Urban Plate are: 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a pizza at Urban Plate, a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice, a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 31 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. A burger at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a burger at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place, a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 31 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, a burger at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 37 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 8 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 37 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pie at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 22 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 37 dollars. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and a pie at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, lasagna at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Mike's Place, pie at Urban Plate, lasagna at Mike's Place are: 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place, a creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate, a creme brulee at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars, 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate and a pie at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 37 dollars.\nThere are 6 variables but only 5 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Mike's Place."}
